Previously on Friends:
How did the job stuff go? He offered me one!
You know what? This calls for a bottle of lsrael's finest!
The job is in Paris.
Oh, God, please, somebody say something.
So if you take this job, you'll be moving to Paris?
Or facing a bitch of a commute.
I know, it's huge, and it's scary and it's really far away from you guys.
But this is such an incredible opportunity for me.
I've already told them about our situation with Emma,
and they said they'll do whatever we need to make us feel comfortable. OK.
I mean, I'll fly back and forth, they'll fly you out. Anything we want.
My boss said I might be getting a new lamp in my cubicle.
All right. We'll work it out. Oh, thank you. Thank you.
You sure this is what you want? I think it is.
What's going on? I got a really incredible job offer.
Hey, great! All right! Good for you!
It's in Paris. What?
No, no, no! No, no, no! No, too much is changing, okay?
First Phoebe getting married. Congratulations.
And then these two move in to a stupid house in the stupid suburbs.
Hey, this afternoon you said you'd be supportive.
It comes and goes. I wouldn't trust it!
You guys, this is really, really important to me.
It means a lot if you could try to get onboard.
Of course we can. Congratulations. Thank you.
Joey?
No, my hugs are reserved for people staying in America!
Joey, it would mean...
No! Get your France-going arms away from me!
Are you okay with this? Well, it makes me feel sad, but...
Talking to Ross. I see.
Rachel moving to another country? Not being able to see her every day?
How could I be okay with this?
But what are we gonna do? She really needs this job.
Do you think if Ralph Lauren offered her her old job back, she would take it?
How's that gonna happen?
Is this the best way to use one of your three magic wishes?
Like, I don't know, I could talk to her boss. Yeah.
I met him at that Christmas party. I mean, we really hit it off.
The guy who kept calling you "Ron"? I didn't say we were brothers!
Hey, Phoebe. Hey. Hi.
Tell me what you think. The house next door to the one that we're buying just went on the market.
I wanna take a look at it, but Chandler doesn't.
We close escrow tomorrow.
So seeing another house can only confuse us. We're easily confused. We're not very bright.
But what if it's better than ours? Shouldn't we at least look?
What do you think, Pheebs?
Well, I think that shirt makes you look like you should work at a Baskin-Robbins.
Anyway....
Hey, isn't Joey's agent Estelle Leonard? Yeah.
She died. You're kidding!
That's terrible. Yeah, last Saturday.
Wow! She was the first black man to fly solo across the Atlantic!
Wait a minute, I read the wrong one. Oh, yeah?
Yeah, she was just an agent.
Joey's gonna be so upset. I know. He always wanted to be the
first black man to cross the Atlantic.
We cannot tell Joey about this.
He's already flipping out about everything changing.
This'll push him over the edge.
Seriously, you don't think we should tell him? Not for a little while.
Let's just give him a few days to get used to everything else.
What if he reads the paper?
Unless Snoopy says it to Charlie Brown, I think we're okay.
May I help you? Yeah. I'm a friend of Rachel Green's.
Actually, we met at the Christmas party about two years ago.
Oh, right. Don? Close. Ron.
Well, what can I do for you?
Well, I'm here to see if you'll give Rachel her job back.
Did she ask you to come here and do this?
First I have to get you to agree...
...then we'll see if she wants to come back.
Wow, that is tempting.
She loved her job here. Let's face it, you're not gonna find anyone who did it as well as she did. Isn't that true?
She is good. I took a shot there.
But I'm sorry, there's nothing I can do.
Oh, that's not true. There's nothing I want to do.
I see.
Thanks very much.
Is this your son? Yeah, his name is Ross.
What? Nothing, it's just that it's close to Ron.
Does little Ross like dinosaurs, by any chance?
Yeah, they're all he talks about. Why?
How would he like to come with me to the Museum of Natural History after everyone else has left, just the two of us...
...and he can touch anything he wants?
I just heard it how you must have heard it, and that's not good.
Let me start again. I'm a paleontologist.
You'll be there with us, and the touching refers only to bones-- fossils!
You could really arrange that? You let Rachel come back and it's done.
I guess having Rachel back wouldn't be the worst thing in the world.
Yes! Thank you! This is great! Thank you so much.
I swear, your kid's gonna have the time of his life.
That's great. I worry about little Ross.
He's always reading, collecting rocks and he's obsessed with dinosaurs.
He'll be fine!
Hey, Pheebs. Hey.
Everything okay? I'm just mad at my agent.
Estelle? Why?
There's a part in this TV movie that I would be perfect for...
...and I didn't even get put up for it. She better have a good reason.
I'm guessing she does.
Well, I wanna hear it, because she keeps doing this.
No, wait, wait, wait! All right, I gotta go.
Just listen. Promise me that you will wait a minute before you call her.
Well, okay. Why?
Because a promise between friends means never having to give a reason.
I love that saying!
Hello? Joey, it's Estelle.
I was just gonna call you. That's weird.
It's a little coincidental, but believable.
Listen, I'm sure you're wondering why I didn't get you an audition for that TV movie.
Yeah, actually I am.
I guess I dropped the ball there.
That's it? You know, it seems like all you do lately is drop the ball.
Don't take that tone with me. Who do you think you are?
Alan Lemon, the first black man to fly solo across the Atlantic?
No, look, all I'm saying is you're my agent...
...and you're not getting me any auditions and I'm tired of it.
What are you saying?
I'm saying that this isn't working for me anymore, okay, Estelle? You're fired. Goodbye.
Man, tough week for Estelle.
Hi. Hi.
Emma left her stuffed T. Rex at my house.
You know she can't sleep without it. Well, she's asleep now.
Stop forcing that thing on her. Okay.
You're not gonna believe what happened to me today!
Ralph Lauren called and gave me my job back!
No! I mean, it was the weirdest thing.
They fire me and then out of nowhere, they just hire me back.
I mean, that place must just be falling apart without me!
So you're not going to Paris? No, I'm still going!
What?
Well, when the Louis Vuitton people found out that Ralph Lauren wanted me back, they offered me more money!
Ross, isn't that great?
Hi. We're buying the house next door. Could we just take a look around?
Sure, I'm showing it to someone else right now, but please, look around.
I feel like we're cheating on our house.
If we cheat, shouldn't it be with a hot, younger house that does stuff that our house won't do?
Ours is so much better!
This living room is smaller, the dining room looks like a cave.
What a hole!
So, what do you think? Love it!
We already have one offer. I think the lady upstairs will make another one.
They could be our neighbors. What are they like?
The woman upstairs is nice. She and her husband have two kids.
He's on Wall Street, and she's a-- Oh... my... God!
Sure.
Hey, Joey, you wanna come with me to--?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I just feel bad about firing Estelle.
This has gotta be killing her.
No, that wouldn't kill her.
A coronary embolism might.
I don't know. She's gotta be taking it hard. I was her only client.
Except for this guy who eats paper.
And I'm guessing he eats more money than he makes.
Look, I know she's not a great agent, but she did stick with me for 10 years.
I'm gonna call her and hire her again. No, no, no! Don't call her.
You wait for her to call you. Why?
Because patience is the road to understanding.
Which is the key to a happy heart.
You blow me away.
All right, so promise you're gonna wait for her to call you?
I promise. Okay.
And that means never having to give a reason.
What a small world!
And yet I never run into Beyoncé.
You two know each other?
We go way back. Before Monica made an honest man out of him, Chandler used to be my little love muffin.
So are you guys thinking of getting this house too?
Are we gonna have a bidding war? I better warn you, I'm a toughie.
Don't-- Don't-- Don't--
No, actually, we are buying the house next door.
Why?
I don't know why.
Oh, that decides it, then! I was on the fence.
But knowing that you two would be our neighbors?
Now we have to get it!
Ellen, we're gonna talk numbers.
This cannot be happening.
The realtor said another couple made an offer.
Maybe the Janices won't get it! Maybe the other couple will.
The only way that'll happen is if the other couple are the Hitlers!
Okay, okay! All right, what if we get both houses?
We can turn this one into a guesthouse! That's a great idea!
By the way, I don't mean to sound distasteful but...
...when did you start crapping money?
You come up with an idea. All right.
We've still got three hours till escrow closes on our house.
We can still get out. But we love our house.
Will we love it so much with her next door?
And she's gonna be louder out here too!
Just the crickets and, "Oh... my... God!"
Okay. But if we don't get this house, she'll still show up wherever we go.
At least if she's here, it eliminates the element of surprise.
Never again will you have to hear the three words...
...that make your balls jump back up inside your body!
Well, we have to do something. We can't have her living next door.
Oh, that does it too.
Who is it?
It's me. Ron.
Look, I know Rachel turned you down...
...but I think there's a way you might be able to get her to come back.
This may surprise you, but rehiring fired employees is not my main job.
Just hear me out.
How would you feel about offering her a raise?
Not good, Ron.
Perhaps I can persuade you.
What if you could give your son...
...this genuine pterodactyl egg replica.
Wow! That's pretty cool.
So? Do we have a deal?
Okay, you got it. Yes! Yes!
This is gonna make me very popular.
Believe me, the ladies, they love it.
I meant with my son.
Good, because the ladies, not so much.
Joey, this is Al Zebooker, the guy who eats paper.
I'm sure you've heard that Estelle passed away.
I wanted to let you know there's a memorial for her...
...at the Westside Chapel tomorrow at 10.
Hope you can make it.
Oh, my God.
Hello? Joey, it's Estelle.
Estelle?
Yeah, I wanted to call and tell you that there's no hard feelings for firing me.
Okay. I just-- I can't believe you're calling me.
I didn't think I should just drop by.
No, no! Don't drop by! Don't drop by!
Anyway, you did what you had to do. I'm okay.
Can I ask you something?
What's it like there?
It's all right.
Look, kiddo, I gotta go.
Good luck with the career. You're gonna be huge!
Thanks for everything, Estelle. Bye.
"Out of area." Boy, I'll say!
Well, I just talked to Sid.
We are definitely putting in an offer on the house.
And I'll bet we get it!
The Hitlers will be so disappointed.
All right, I gotta run. Tell Monica I say goodbye.
I'll see you later, neighbor.
Wait!
I just want you to know that I'm so happy you're going to be here.
Oh, me too!
Because...
...that way...
...we can pick up where we left off.
I never stopped loving you.
Oh... my-- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I want you.
I need you.
I must have you, Janice Litman-Goralnik neé Hosenstein.
Chandler, what are you talking about?
Now that you live next door, we can be together every day.
Sid and Monica never have to know a thing.
I don't know what to say.
I mean, you know, obviously we have this heat between us.
Obviously.
But I love my husband.
And I know you love your wife.
I don't think we should get this house now.
Don't say that. Don't dangle the dream and take it away.
Chandler, one of us has got to be strong.
I understand.
Although....
Maybe just one last moment of weakness.
Goodbye, Chandler Bing.
They're never coming down now!
Hi. Hi!
You are never going to believe what happened to me today.
What?
Ralph Lauren called, again, and they offered me more money.
They did? Yes! It was the weirdest thing.
Zelner called me and said, "We will do anything we can to get you back."
And that I should thank some "Ron."
I don't even know what department that guy's in!
So, what are you gonna do? Well, I took it!
That's great! So you're staying in New York!
You're excited, right? You know-- Look, the money's great.
It's certainly the easier choice. Right.
But, you know, I mean, was I looking forward to going to Paris? Sure.
Was I excited about working in the fashion capital of the world?
Oh, absolutely.
Yeah, but you know, this is....
It's fine. I'm fine going back to a job where I've pretty much gotten everything out of it that I possibly can.
I had no idea--
I had no idea you were so excited about Paris.
I mean, you said you were scared.
I mean, it was "good" scared, though, you know?
I mean, like "when I moved to New York" scared.
Or "when I found out I was gonna have Emma" scared.
But this is fine. This is gonna be good.
You should go.
What?
It's what you want. You should go.
You really think so?
I really do.
But I already told Zelner that I would come back.
I'm sure he'll understand.
All right. All right! I'm gonna do it! I'm gonna go to Paris!
Yeah. Yeah.
I'm going to Paris!
Thank you, Ross. Yeah, yeah.
Oh, I'm so happy.
Then I'm happy too.
Thank you all for coming.
We're here today to pay our respects to a wonderful agent...and a beautiful woman.
Inside.
As Estelle's only two clients, we would like to say a few words.
Dude, where's my speech?
That is entertaining. Al Zebooker, everybody!